[{"answer": "Well, that's such a lovely introduction.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "You know, I find that so sad that it has now become a racial question.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "I suppose the obvious question to -- the obvious question to that is it a white or black Santa Claus given all the controversy at the moment?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, you have to go sometime.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Where are you going?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "This is our 21st year.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Who do you think is the most controversial entries?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "I like Miley Cyrus.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Miley Cyrus, you know, Miley Cyrus and the tongue?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "While you've touched on it to a degree.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Why is he struggling so much to really fulfill the great flame of ambition and excitement that he was elected on originally in 2009?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Well, you know, that what's so fascinating and it depends on what side you're on.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Do you think he's a hero or a villain or a bit of both?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, I should point out that much as we would have loved to have interviewed the pope, he has not done an interview.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "What do you make of him?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "It's a sign of some changes in the Catholic Church.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Is that a sign you think of a whole new papacy, a whole new Catholic church going forward?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "She's an absolute breath of fresh air, isn't she?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Well, first of all she has said, \"I don't know what's going to come out of my mouth.\"", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What do you make of her?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I am a fan of both of this.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "They're very divisive as a couple, aren't they?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "I'm with you.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Are you laughing with me or at me?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Well, I like controversial.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "What is your personal criteria for selection?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Can you give me even a tiny clue who's number one?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Yes that was pretty good, that was pretty good I love Hugh Jackman.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "What about Hugh Jackman giving you a lap dance?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Oh please, you know, as I said to people, if -- (inaudible) had interviewed Michael Thatcher would you have said, \"Have seen this hanky panky?\"", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "There may have been a little fling between you, any truth in that?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "... yes I mean I do, shoulda, coulda, woulda.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "... why did I do that?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "The Pope has never done an interview, Queen Elizabeth has never done an interview.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Number five, who would you most like to interview, you've never been able to get to?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Jennifer Lawrence that would be nice.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Jennifer Lawrence?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Let me just see who we're talking about.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Number seven, if you can invite three people from all the people you've interviewed to a dream dinner party, who would you go for?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "You know I'm not good at the biggest or the worst of that, you know, I remember an interview that I did with Clint Eastwood.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Who's the biggest star you've ever meet?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "This is a great -- it's a great question for you because you've ...", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "(Inaudible) best and worst and worst and best, if could drop in a dessert island what?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Beethoven's Night I guess because it's just, you know, it's so bombastic and it would get me out of my depression to hear that.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "And which man would you have to accompany you?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "... I would be first there -- no I never have so I would read the Bible.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I don't think there should be any president who runs the country in perpetuity, that's what someone to fool about our government.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Who is the one you would most like to run the country in perpetuity?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "I really don't know the reason why.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Do have any explanation for why your daughter just had her tonsils out and now laying in this terrible condition?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Well, as a family, our faith is so strong that we don't even think about the possibility of death.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "What would you say as a family to that?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Well, I think first, it's important to know that Jahi is a person not evidence and that's part what's been troubling the family.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "What is the legal position in terms of who has the final say of what happens now to Jahi?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Well, I know when I've touched her feet I can take my fingernail and run it up her feet and she'll move them.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "ORGAN: Are you seeing any sign, Nailah, that she is aware of what is happening or can hear you or is reacting in any way which might suggest that she is not as the hospital believe brain dead?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Well, Piers it's just an awful tragic situation.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "How do we -- how does it get resolved?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Well, I'm a little tufty that I'm not in studio with you Piers.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "How are you Ms. Coulter?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "It's a joke Piers.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "What is that mean?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Well, I'd say he's Jewish.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "So, you would say unequivocally, Jesus Christ was White as well?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "The fact.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Well, is he white?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "I just said it.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "Was he white?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "That's a fact.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Oh is he White?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I just said it.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Was he White?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "Well, I don't --", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "But was he white?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "No, I think you're mad.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "(inaudible) do you feel uncomfortable with this debate?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "I'm not sure, I mean in Rush Limbaugh's case, we of course think he is the Pope.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Why would this embrace the likes of Rush Limbaugh?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "I think it manifestly because of ObamaCare, people are loosing their health insurance and their health premiums are going up.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "What is going on here and how does it end?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "I have no idea who might win it.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "What doing you think are going to be the key moments now in the next couple of years which can determine what type of republican candidate faces the final run off and who might win it?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Well, if I had and then I had won.", "docId": "131217pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Have you intend to get down there and buy a ticket?", "qSentId": 642}]